I'm not sure I agree with that.
OK.
I think if you're democratically amending
the Constitution per the rules of the Constitution,
that's fine.
If we could find a constitutional way
to get rid of the Second Amendment, I'd be pro that.
So let's pose a hypothetical wherein
the entire population of the United States
has drastically changed.
Yes.
And the population now has completely different intentions
about what to do with the country.
Let's say it wants to give it all back to Mexico,
dismantling the United States of America.
If that's the case, then what's the use of the Constitution?
It hasn't defended the country.
In fact, it's allowed for its destruction.
I don't understand the premise.
How did the whole country change?
Demographic replacement.
Mass migration.
I mean, we're seeing a change in demographics.
And there's-
What is the-
I do want to talk about immigration today.
I hope we talk about it.
Everyone's itching in this group to get to immigration.
Yes, sir.
I've saved it.
I've saved it for you all.
But given we're on the sense of the Constitution,
and you asked a question, what is the proportion
of immigrants in this country?
What proportion of the population is foreign born?
It's very difficult to measure, because the actual projections
of the number have been changing more rapidly.
But what is currently the best estimate of official-
I think it was about 15%.
Yes.
Just under 15%.
Which is, by the way, which is more, actually,
than the original estimate was.
But 15% of the people are going to change the country,
change the Constitution.
How's that going to make sense?
It's actually a nightmare.
As someone who wants to amend the Constitution
and get rid of things like the ridiculous way
the Senate is set up, or the Second Amendment on guns,
or various other things, it's really hard
to change the Constitution.
They made it almost impossible.
You know the last time we had a Constitutional Amendment?
You know what?
Like 20, 30 years ago.
I understand.
And it was all, I think, members of Congress paying.
Which is why-
It's impossible.
No, I get it.
So where are you getting this scenario where
350-odd million people all become foreign-born migrants,
or the children of migrants, immediate migrants,
even though America is a nation of migrants,
and then abandon the Constitution
and give the country back to Mexico?
Outside of your imagination, where is that happening?
Well, let's bring it back to the actual discussion.
What you did is you entertained my hypothetical.
But then instead of sticking to the point of the Constitution,
you said, well, how would you bring about your hypothetical?
And then when I gave you-
Because you missed out the part where the Constitution's
quite hard to change.
Hold on.
I understand that.
I gave you a simple-
I also wanted to get a sense of where you are,
and you're a great replacement guy, so that's fine.
OK.
Yeah, and you're a real good journalist
because you don't talk to people who identify
as like a political ideology.
I mean, that's a very literal idea.
No, I don't debate fascists.
I'll talk to them, but I wouldn't debate them.
Frankly, that's upsetting.
I think there's a big problem when, you know,
we value freedom of speech so much,
but any real journalist is not going to talk to somebody
because they identify with a politically incorrect ideology.
Just talk to the guy in front of you.
What are you talking about?
You literally stop talking to him,
and then everybody has to vote him out.
Debating versus talking is very different.
It's pointless, right?
He doesn't believe in free speech.
OK.
He doesn't believe in democracy.
He was freely speaking with you.
You're the one who shut up.
No, he said it very clearly.
OK, so I support free speech so that I can get one election.
After one election, my guy comes in,
and after my guy comes in, nobody gets to speak or vote again.
Why would I debate that?
We listened to your conversation.
Well, I'm reminding you what it was said,
because you just misrepresented it.
Let's bring it back to the Constitution.
Please do.
First, fourth, fifth, 14th amendments.
Those are the ones I'm saying Trump is defying.
Do you support that, or do you deny them?
I believe that the Constitution is valuable
because it represents particular interests of the founding
stock of Americans who made this country great.
Do you think due process is important?
Some would say that's at the very core of American
Constitution, Fifth Amendment.
And what I think makes the Constitution function,
what allows it to save this country
and to actually make it work, are the people who are.
I'm not sure where you're going with this argument.
Is Trump defying the Constitution?
That's my claim.
You can have these weird hypotheticals about it.
We're taking it into a different meta, which is,
what's the function of the Constitution?
I'd rather not have your-
You already did.
You already did, literally just five minutes ago
when you took it to immigration, pal.
Okay, let's bring it back.
I want to bring it back to the first, the fourth,
the fifth, and the 14th amendments,
and the 22nd amendments.
Then let me throw it to your question.
You've got two very good positions here.
One is to say, I don't think he's defying them,
and I'll say why you're wrong.
Or you say, I don't care that he's defying them,
as one of your colleagues said, in which case,
I don't know where this conversation goes
because you don't believe in democracy.
That's fair.
Do you think it's wrong to dismantle the Constitution?